Olha Haidamaka



ELT Specialist

My Contact

 \boxtimes

odpiskun@gmail.com



+3530877422984



Millicent Rd, Clane, Co.Kildare Ireland



linkedin.com/in/olhahaidamaka-905a0414b

Expertise

- Communicative Approach
- Lexical Approach
- Test Teach Test (TTT)
- Task Based Learning (TBL)
- Flipped classroom

Language

- Ukrainian (fluent)
- Russian (fluent)
- English (fluent)
- German (basic)

Certificate

Certificate of Proficiency in English

Cambridge University Press & Assessment English

Issued Feb 2021

 Certificate in Teaching English to Speakers of Other Languages (CELTA)

Cambridge University Press & Assessment Issued Jul 2019

• TKT - Modules 1,2,3

Cambridge University Press & Assessment English Issued Jan 2019

About Me

As a dedicated and energetic English teacher with 6+ years of experience in EFL and ESL at all levels and different age groups (10-75yr), I love taking on new professional challenges. I have a background of teaching Business and Corporate English in a one-to-one and group contexts. Throughout my career, I have been constantly innovating and experimenting with course design, teaching methods and approaches, creating my own supplementary materials. As well as loving to see my students' growth and development of their English skills, I extremely enjoy sharing my knowledge with my peers and playing a part in their professional development.

Professional Experience

Zone3000 | English Coach

Mar 2018 - Present

- Taught people in different English level groups (from A1 to C1)
- Developed and implemented curriculums for different courses from scratch (Grammar Course for CS Specialists, Conversation Club, Boardgames Club, Grammar Intensive Crash Course)
- Experience in modern approaches and methods of effective foreign languages teaching
- Consulted teachers on teaching techniques and new approaches
- Organized and was the leader of the Speaking Club for would-be CS Specialists
- Written feedback based on progress tests and regular checks during the studying process
- Developed supplementary materials for coursebooks in collaboration with other teachers
- Taught Grammar Lectures for the employees.
- Worked as a committed, responsible and proactive member of the team

Green Forest | Junior Teacher

Sep 2017 - Dec 2018

- Taught students of A1 and B2 levels.
- Assessed students' effort.
- Gave feedback on students' achievements and areas to develop.
- Kept track of attendance and progress during the course.

Education Background

2017 – 2018 V. N. Karazin Kharkiv National University

Master's degree, Philology

2013 – 2017 H. S. Skovoroda Kharkiv National Pedagogical University

Bachelor of Philology, Teacher of the English Language and ForeignLiterature